drperlmutter.com 2018-12-17

# Privacy Policy - David Perlmutter M.D.

## General

This site is a service of Dr. Perlmutter Group (“DPG”).

This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us using this web site or any other DPG site (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected elsewhere, including offline and on web sites linked to or from the Site.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By using or accessing the Site, and/or by registering with the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use our Site or provide any information to us.

In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please also read our Terms of Use. Your use of our Site constitutes your agreement to the Terms of Use.

We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will give you notice of the revised Privacy Policy by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site and by revising the “Last Updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for regularly reviewing the current privacy policy. Any change, update or modification we make will be effective immediately upon posting on our Site. Your continued access of our Site after we post any changes or revisions constitutes your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California customers to request certain information regarding our disclosures of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. The law provides that we may (1) respond to this request by proving certain information about our disclosures, or (2) if we maintain an opt- out or opt-in procedure, by providing customers with a cost-free means to exercise that right.

To make such a request, please contact us at webmaster@drperlmuttergroup.com, or the address below, and provide your name and the address to which you would like us to respond.

Dr Perlmutter Group  
Attention: Web Master/800 Goodlette Rd North #270  
Naples, FL 34102 USA

## Collection of Information

We collect “automatic information” and “personally identifiable information.”  
“Automatic information” is information automatically collected by our web server (which may be hosted by a third-party) that your web browser makes available whenever you visit our Site, such as the IP address of your computer, your operating system version and browser type, the duration of your visit to the Site, and other standard tracking data we use to evaluate site traffic and usage patterns.

The Site also uses “cookies,” which are bits of data sent by a website through the browser to the computer of the user visiting the site, that enable our Site to return the results the browser expects. Most website browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able to turn off the cookie acceptance option in your browser’s settings. However, disabling the cookie support function of the browser may prevent some portions of our Site from functioning properly, and you may not be able to fully utilize our Site. We may from time to time use advertising companies to develop banner ads for our Site. These ads may contain cookies that may be sent to your browser through the banner ads. We do not have control over cookies placed by our advertisers, nor do we have access to any information their cookies may collect.

“Personally identifiable information” is information that tells us who you are, such as your name, job title, company, physical mailing address, e-mail address, telephone and fax numbers and, if applicable, financial information such as your credit card information. We may collect this information when you:

  * register to attend DPG trade shows, conferences and events;
  * subscribe to our publications, including e-newsletters;
  * register with our Site;
  * communicate with us by e-mail;
  * post comments, ratings or messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards or forums;
  * and/or complete online forms, surveys or contest entries.

You always have the option not to provide the personal information we request. If you choose not to provide the personal information we request, you can still visit our Site, but you may be unable to access or use certain options and/or services.

## Use and Disclosure of Personal and Financial Information

If you elect to provide personal information to us, we may use it for the purpose for which it was provided (e.g., to establish your account, send you publications to which you have subscribed, attribute content you submit to the Site to you, etc.), and for the other purposes set forth herein. We may use personally identifiable information to (1) send you e-mails about your account; (2) respond to e-mails; (3) provide customer support; and (4) perform other similar functions. We may also use personally identifiable information to send you marketing, advertising and/or product/service offerings (“Commercial Communications”).

We may share personally identifiable information with our affiliates and with our partners, including our exhibitors, sponsors and advertisers, for marketing, advertising, and/or product/service offering purposes. While we will seek to require all such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies consistent with this Privacy Policy, and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, DPG does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties.

If you wish to limit the Commercial Communications you receive from us and/or our affiliates and partners, and/or do not wish to have your personally identifiable information shared with third parties, you may opt (i) not to have your personally identifiable information shared with third parties, (ii) not to receive Commercial Communications from third parties, and/or (iii) not to receive Commercial Communications from us except for Commercial Communications related to the product or service for which you provided your personally identifiable information, as described below under ”Opt-Out Option.”

We may also disclose personally identifiable information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may have breached our Terms of Use, or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other users of our Site, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose personally identifiable information when we reasonably believe that the law requires it.

In addition, as our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by DPG, or any subsidiary or affiliated entity, are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, personally identifiable information may be among the transferred assets.

If you submit financial information to us, we may use that information to verify your credit and collect payments for your purchases, orders, registrations, etc. We may share your financial information with third parties that process financial transactions on our behalf.

## Automatic Information

We will use automatic information to personalize our Site based on the preferences you submit to us at the time you register. We also use the aggregated information to evaluate products and services we may offer to you.

We may use temporary, session-specific cookies to ensure visits to our Site are smooth and customized for the visitor â for example, to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on our Site, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personalization information. Cookies allow us to provide a visitor’s browser with information tailored to the visitor’s preferences and needs. We also may use permanent or persistent cookies that remain on a visitor’s computer after the visitor leaves our Site.

In addition, we reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, and to otherwise administer our Site.

## Aggregated Information

We reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

## Information on Children

The Site is a general audience web site. We do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from users of this Site who are under the age of thirteen. If we become aware that a user of our web site is under the age of 13 and has provided any personally identifiable information to us without verification of parental consent, we will remove that child’s personal information from our files.

## Updating Visitor Information

Many of our Site functions (but not all) allow you to correct, update and modify your personal and/or financial information. If you would like instructions on how you may correct, update and modify your personal and/or financial information, please contact us at webmaster@drperlmuttergroup.com and provide us with the specific Site through which you provided information. If you would like to update your information via e-mail, please contact us at webmaster@divcom.com, and provide us with (1) the name and e-mail address you previously provided to us, and (2) any updates to your personal and/or financial information.

You may not change your username ID selected at registration for a trade show, event or conference.

## Third Party and Affiliated Links

Our Site may from time to time contain links to other websites, including suppliers, advertisers and affiliates. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, the content of, or information gathered by, these other websites. We do not endorse any of these websites or the products or services associated with such websites merely because they are linked to our Site.

## Information Posted on Bulletin Boards and Other Forums

Users of our Site should be aware that information you disclose on bulletin boards and other forums may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited messages from others.

## Opt-Out Option

If you do not want DPG to share your personally identifiable information with third parties, or if you do not wish to receive Commercial Communications from DPG and/or third parties, you may (i) state your preferences at the time you submit your personal information to us, or (ii) change your preferences at any time by (a) notifying us in writing (at the Privacy Policy Contact mailing address or email address below) of your e-mail address and of your preference that we not share your information and/or that you do not wish to receive such Commercial Communications from DPG and/or third parties, or (b) following the unsubscribe instructions contained within the e-mail you receive from us.

We will update your preferences as soon as is reasonably practicable.

We will use reasonable efforts to forward your opt-out request (including your e-mail address) to the specific third-party marketer whose offer you received from us prompting your opt-out or unsubscribe request, so that it can include your e-mail address on its own do-not-email list. However, even if you opt-out as described above, we will not be able to remove your personal information from the databases of third parties with which we have already shared your personal information (i.e., to which we have provided your personal information prior to our receipt of your opt-out request). DPG does not bear any responsibility for ensuring that any third party complies with your opt-out or unsubscribe request vis-a-vis its own lists.

## Security and Encryption

Unfortunately, information transmitted on the Internet and/or stored on systems attached to the Internet is not 100% secure. As a result, DPG cannot ensure, warrant or guarantee the security or integrity of such information.

## Privacy Policy Contact

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by letter at the address below, or by e-mail at webmaster@drperlmuttergroup.com

Dr Perlmutter Group  
Attention: Web Master/800 Goodlette Rd North #270  
Naples, FL 34102 USA
